Ahmed Sherif

Backend Developer

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Backend Developer with +1 year of experience developing, and implementing applications and solutions using a range of technologies and programming languages. Seeking a challenging position in a dynamic company with a professional outlook where my education and ambition can be exploited and my experience maximized.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer.

March 2021 - Apr 2021.

Visions-Tech.

• Full Stack Developer.

Backend Developer.

Jul 2021 - Des 2021.

Serve₅.

 Backend developer via PHP-Laravel in "serv5", Did a strong role in client side missions.

Backend Developer.

June 2022 - Current.

Al-Motawereen.

• Backend developer with a startup

"Al-Motawereen" Working on Strong Role in a legal consulting system.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- PHP
- Laravel
- OOP, Data Structure.
- MySql
- mvc, mvvm)
- Vue.js
- Wordpress
- git, GitHub, Bitbucket, GitLab, Jira

Phone

:(+20) 1118817589 - (+20) 1069861264 Email :ahmed.hussein.202050@gmail.com LinkedIn : linkedin.com/in/ahmed-sherif97

: Nasr City, Cairo, Egypt

EDUCATION

Bsc of Electrical Systems and Computer Science.

Jun. 2021.

Persistent.

Passion. Teamwork.

Address

AL-AZHAR UNIVERSITY, Egypt.

• Grade: Excellent.

PROJECTS

- **Travveo** A Hotels Booking website.
- **SOIN** An E-commerce website.
- Mashora An E-commerce website.

COURSES

- Vue.js v3 (the complete guide) by Maximili an Schwarz müller
- Laravel 8 from scratch by Laracasts.
- Full Stack diploma (PHP stack) with **Route Academy**

LANGUAGES

Arabic: Native.

• English: Intermediate.

MILITARY STATUS

Exempted.

REFERENCES

References and documents are available upon request.

Soft Skills

- Leadership.
- Fast Learning.